- This season, get ready
for a Bachelorette
like we've never had before.
- Whoo!
Yeah!
- [chanting]
Hannah! Hannah! Hannah! Hannah!
- Hannah's about as real
as it gets.
She's not an actress.
She's not a movie star.
She's just a real girl
that's looking for love.
- Part the seas.
Hannah B. is coming at you.
both: Oh!
- The chemistry that
I'm already having with her,
it's off the charts.
- Oh, my freak!
- Hannah is sincere.
- What is wrong with me?
- Totally honest.
- You can cut that sexual
tension with a knife.
- Ooh!
- [laughing]
- And she's ready to tell it
like it is.
- None of you know
anything about me
and what makes me me and things
that I've gone through.
'Cause nobody's even asked.
'Cause all we do is talk
about stupid [bleep].
So figure it out or, like,
I don't want to do this.
I'm a normal human being,
like, trying to be
the Bachelorette,
and I don't know what to do.
And I'm scared.
[crying]
- Tonight it's the dramatic
season premiere
of "The Bachelorette."
- [sniffling]
[dramatic music]
And it all started
like this...
♪
[phone trilling]
- Oh, my Go--
[laughing]
- What are you doing?
- Um, I don't know why I'm
talking to you, Chris Harrison.
[laughs]
- Well, I know that the, uh--
I was talking to some
of the producers and--and
we've been talking
about "Bachelorette."
Uh, what do you think?
Are you serious about it?
- I want it, yeah.
- You do?
Well, should we do it?
You want to be
the Bachelorette?
♪
- I--yeah.
Are you asking me?
- I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
You're the Bachelorette.
- [giggles]
[stammering]
No--n--
Are you seri--
- I'm dead serious.
[uplifting music]
Congratulations, Hannah.
You're the Bachelorette.
- What?
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
- [laughing]
- Mom, I'm the Bachelorette!
♪
- Are you for real?
- [laughing]
God, it's so weird.
Um...
- Who's the Bachelorette?
- I'm the Bachelorette?
I can't even say it.
[laughing]
Oh, my gosh.
[country music]
♪
Being the Bachelorette
is so surreal.
Part of me still has this
mentality of, "Why me?"
Like, I can already, like,
feel my heart, like,
freaking out.
I don't know what to do
with my hands.
[laughs]
Ah!
For some reason, I always
put pressure on myself.
[laughs]
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm nervous.
♪
Everybody has different ways
that they find their person,
and I am really hopeful
that this is mine.
♪
- Tuscaloosa city limits
right here.
- That's right.
This is the big city.
I never got a hometown.
- This is it.
- But I'm having a hometown
with Chris Harrison.
- Yeah, this is your hometown.
There you go.
- Roll tide!
I love Tuscaloosa,
and I am so appreciative
of growing up here because
it made me who I am.
- You guys proud
of this girl right here?
- Very, very proud.
- Really?
Being the Bachelorette
is, like, so overwhelming
and it feels so weird.
- I don't know what
you're gonna do with 25 guys,
but I'm excited to see,
'cause you got this, girl.
- I am just a normal girl
looking for somebody
to spend
the rest of my life with.
- So you do performances here,
like dance, sing?
- Pageants.
First pageant was here.
- Oh, really?
- Yep.
As a kid, I loved to perform.
But I never felt good enough.
- Hannah Brown.
[cheers and applause]
- I thought I needed
to be perfect.
[cheers and applause]
So I honestly never thought
I would be Miss Alabama.
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic music]
When I won Miss Alabama,
I was so happy.
But it wasn't, like,
my goal in life.
♪
I wanted to find somebody that
I want to be with forever.
♪
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hannah.
- Nice to meet you.
Colton.
- With Colton, I was
struggling to be perfect.
- Yeah, roll tide.
- All right.
What is your greatest fear?
- Like, not being enough at,
like, everything that I do.
- I've been there, too.
So I know it's your birthday.
- Mm-hmm.
- So we are going
to make a toast.
- Okay.
[laughs]
I can't do this.
- I don't want you to feel
like you have to be perfect.
I--I want to see the good,
the bad, everything.
I want to see--
- And the hot mess that I am.
- And the hot mess.
I do, because that's life.
- For the first time,
I realized that I can
be enough just being myself.
♪
[laughing]
Even though it didn't
work out with Colton,
I really grew personally
and found out,
like, who I am to my core.
Raise your hand if dancing
makes you happy.
- We all do.
- You all do, yeah.
I just want to encourage
each one of you
to always be a part
of something
that makes you happy.
I want my time
as the Bachelorette--
my experience here
to feel different
because I am different.
♪
It's really important for me
to find a man
that will love me
for all of me.
♪
Bless the man who spends
forever with me,
because I'm so much to handle.
But what I want to give
somebody is really special.
♪
I'm nervous...
but expectant.
I've got to be
completely myself.
And the desire of my heart
is to find love.
♪
I don't know what I'm doing,
but bring on the men.
♪
[laughs]
- Coming up tonight...
- ♪ It's your boy Cam
♪ And I'm back on the mic
- Oh!
- Meet the men Hannah
will drive wild.
- [both snarling]
- They're just making me feel
really special.
[screams]
- [laughs]
- Will it be love
at first sight?
- I'm seriously really,
really into you.
So you--you got some
catching up to do.
- I have a total crush.
- You bet.
I don't even know
what to say right now.
I'm really excited about us.
- [laughing]
- On a night
full of surprises.
- Are you ready to do this?
- No way.
- Yes.
- When "The Bachelorette"
season premiere continues.
[upbeat music]
[overlapping chatter,
whooping]
- Ah!
- So pretty!
- Ow, ow, ow!
- Demi and Katie are visiting
me to put me
in a really good head space
for tonight.
- To Hannah slaying these men.
And roll tide!
Cheers.
- And go Tigers.
- I truly am excited
to meet 30 different guys.
And if it's a train wreck,
it's a train wreck.
I can laugh about it later.
But I'm trying not
to put pressure
on myself for anything.
- Your energy is so easy
to feel good around...
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- That I think that you're
gonna bring it out
of all those guys,
even if they are nervous,
like, the first night.
Oh, my God,
you could be meeting
your future husband tonight.
- Will be meeting
her future husband.
- Oh, my God!
What?
No!
- Demi and Katie just pumped
me up for one of the biggest
nights of my life.
They're always so helpful,
and I am so excited
to meet these guys.
- Hey, everybody,
Ryan here.
It's the day before I fly out
for "The Bachelorette,"
and I can't be more excited.
I'm here with a farewell party
with my closest friends
and family.
[all cheering]
- Are you gonna miss me,
Manuel?
Huh?
[kisses]
I'm packing.
You gonna miss me?
- Got bags packed,
and we're off to the airport.
Let's go.
- See ya later.
I am super stoked.
Hannah is awesome.
She's without a doubt somebody
I could see spending
the rest of my life with.
[exciting music]
- On the way to California
right now
to meet the Bachelorette.
It's freaking awesome.
♪
- Hey, I'm Tyler.
I'm 26 years old.
I'm a general contractor
in Jupiter, Florida.
But I'm not your
average contractor.
[new wave music]
I love to dance.
I was, like, two classes away
from being a dance minor
at Wake Forest and, uh,
it just puts you out there,
and you're vulnerable and
that's just what I love to do.
Me and Kevin Bacon
are like offspring
when it comes to dancing.
♪
I am so stoked that Hannah B.'s
gonna be the Bachelorette.
You know, I just think
she's drop dead gorgeous.
I think us both being
outgoing and expressive
with ourselves,
that'll really allow us
to connect.
I'm definitely gonna get
the first dance with her.
So I'm looking forward to that.
[dramatic music]
- I'm Peter.
I'm 27.
I live in Westlake Village,
California.
And I'm an airline pilot.
I've always wanted to be
a pilot ever since I was
a little kid growing up
in an aviation family.
My dad's a pilot.
My mom was a flight attendant.
I knew it was what I was gonna
do for the rest of my life.
I'm coming for you, Hannah.
I'm a very spontaneous person.
I can just hop on a plane
and be like,
"Hey, we wanna go there,
or, "We wanna go there."
Or let's go get lunch in,
you know, uh,
New Orleans.
We'll get some crawfish.
I look forward to sharing
that spontaneity
and sense of adventure.
I'm so excited to meet Hannah.
She just seems like such
a genuine, real person.
She's got that, like,
goofy side to her
that to me is so attractive.
That's the mansion
right there.
Hannah, I'm coming for you!
♪
- Bachelorette,
here I come.
Whoo!
I'm Mike Johnson,
Air Force veteran,
Texas resident.
Welcome to my city, Dallas.
When I got the Air Force,
I became a portfolio manager.
Yeah, you went up 5.7%.
I've been focusing
on my career.
My dating life has been
Macaulay Culkin--"Home Alone."
[laughs] I haven't dated
much at all.
I'm so excited and so ready
to go to the mansion
and just meet my bride-to-be.
But there is one woman that I
gotta say see you later to.
She was the first woman
I ever fell in love with.
She's so gorgeous.
- Hey, boy.
Oh, good to see you, Mike.
- Nice seeing you.
You're looking good.
My great grandmother.
Do you have any advice for me?
- Well, just make sure
she's a happy lady.
- A happy lady?
- And listen.
- Yeah, pay attention.
- I can listen.
- Okay, I can do that.
I got big ears for a reason.
Growing up with all these
strong women in my household,
I've learned so much--how
to listen and pay attention
to the small details
and knowing
that you're gonna be wrong
and sucking it up
and dealing with it.
Gonna get my lady, and I'll
bring her back to you, okay?
- Okay, I want to see her.
- I love you, now.
- I love you, too.
- Hi, I'm Joe Barsano,
and I sell boxes.
[beeping]
I'm the box king, baby.
I got all your packaging needs.
Who needs a box?
You need a box?
Moving?
I got a box for that.
Just got dumped?
You wanna put your junk
in a box?
I got that.
And the junk, too.
[laughs]
- Oh, hun, who wants
to try a meatball?
- Mom, I want
to try a meatball.
You're the best cook I know.
I come from a strong Italian
family where my mother,
she was so supportive.
This is my father,
also Joe Barsano.
- How you doing?
- Taught me everything
I needed to know about boxes.
My parents have
a great relationship.
My sisters have
That's what I'm looking for.
- I hope you get the last rose.
- I'm so excited to meet
the Bachelorette.
- Give me all the kids!
Her personality is amazing.
Great energy like mine.
She's beautiful!
[cow mooing]
- Hey, I'm Matt Donald.
Welcome to the farm.
What's up, ladies?
This is the closest I get
to taking girls out to dinner.
[cows mooing]
People describe me as,
you know, quite easy-going.
I'm not the type
to put myself out there
and approach women first,
so this is definitely gonna be
something romantic--
I'm out of my comfort zone.
Going to L.A.
I actually grew up
in a deaf household.
I have two deaf parents.
I have a deaf older brother.
My family and I have been
watching "The Bachelor"
and "The Bachelorette"
since day one.
- [laughs]
- My family loves
the Alabama Crimson Tide.
When Hannah B. gave
the Roll tide toast,
I think a little bit inside
of me was just like,
"Oh, my gosh,
I think I'm already
starting to fall for her."
So the next time I come home,
maybe be with the Bachelorette.
Be true to yourself, yeah.
- It starts with attitude.
If you think you can,
you will.
All right,
let's sell some cars, man.
[applause]
- I'm Connor.
I'm 28 years old.
And I'm the district sales
manager for one of the biggest
automotive brands
in the country.
I really pour
a lot into my career,
but my family anchors me.
How long have you and Boon Boon
been married?
- 50 years.
- 50 years?
- Wow.
- I come from a really
diverse family.
My dad is blond-haired,
blue-eyed from Iowa,
and my mom is from Hong Kong.
My grandparents came over
from China with very little.
It's a classic American tale
of immigrants coming over
and being successful.
Do you think I'm ready
to get married?
- Yeah.
This is a really unorthodox
thing to do,
but I'm willing to put my life
on hold to find the girl
of my dreams.
- 13, two more.
14, 15.
That's it. Stop.
[weights rattling]
- I'm Luke,
I'm 24,
and I live in Gainesville,
Georgia.
I like to think
I'm a good-looking guy.
And when I was in college,
a lot of the girls around me
thought so, too,
and I definitely
took advantage of that.
But I just was getting
a whole lot of emptiness.
This emptiness overcame me and
I had an encounter with God.
I was in the shower,
and God was speaking to me.
I realized that I wasn't
the man that I wanted to be.
[soft music]
And I've been working on being
the husband that I want to be
for my future wife.
Aww, you're so cute.
- Uncle Luke.
- You're so cute.
- My brother and my
sister-in-law met
and got married within
the same year.
And that's why this
is exciting
because I know that the same
could happen for me.
And I'm ready to get married.
Hey, just packing here
with my cute little niece.
Hannah B.
is obviously gorgeous.
We share a lot
of the same values.
White shirt or blue shirt?
- [cooing]
- You like the blue, huh?
I knew you had good taste.
Gimme some.
I'm so ready to get
to know Hannah.
And I'm ready to see
if I'm the one.
- Just landed in L.A.
Time to meet the Bachelorette.
I'm pretty freaking nervous.
- Getting those butterflies
right now.
Sitting in L.A. traffic
waiting for love.
[voice breaks]
- I'm really excited. I'm--
My voice keeps doing this
and that's real natural.
- I may projectile vomit
in front of millions of people.
- I'm gonna meet
my future wife!
Whoo!
- Coming up next...
[pop]
- Oh!
- Roll tide!
- The men arrive.
- Hi!
A tractor!
- Bringing everything
they've got.
- Somebody's already jumping
fences for me.
- It's fun.
- Yes!
Don't touch my junk.
Not yet.
- It's romantic.
- Damn, that was kinda sexy.
Ooh!
- It's all about making
a great first impression.
- I'm here for you.
- I feel it.
[both laughing]
- Until something goes wrong.
- We need to talk.
- Ooh, oh damn.
- I would not want
to be him right now.
- If you're trying
to hide something,
the truth's gonna come out.
- How dare you, like,
think this is okay?
- That definitely
kills the mood for the night.
- Like, that sucks.
She feels betrayed.
- Anybody feeling more nervous?
- I'm pretty nervous about it.
- I could be going home
without ever getting
to know her.
- It's not looking good.
- It's all coming up tonight
when "The Bachelorette"
season premiere continues.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I can't believe tonight's
finally here.
It's really...happening.
It feels like a dream.
I'm so excited
to meet these men.
I'm here for the real deal--
someone to share a life with,
to love me and to love
them back unconditionally.
That is what I want.
- Excitement levels
are getting up there.
Let's go.
- Roll tide!
[all cheering]
♪
- Hannah.
- Hey, Chris.
- Welcome back to the mansion.
- Long time no see.
- Good to see you.
- [laughing]
- This is all you now.
- Yeah.
I'm so nervous.
- Are you freaking out?
- Uh...
- What are you nervous about?
- Well, it's just, like,
probably not
gonna be like normal.
[laughs]
And it just might
not go perfect.
And I need that to be okay.
- Well, let me just let you
off the hook right now.
It's not gonna be perfect.
- Yeah.
- Nothing is.
- So it's all good.
- It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be good.
- So what's your greatest fear
here?
- I'm gonna be real,
so somebody's not going to
equally be as real with me,
I guess.
- Okay.
Do you have a type?
- No, I think, like,
southern is comfortable,
but that hasn't
worked out for me.
- Try a few different flavors.
You never know.
- Absolutely.
Confetti cake it.
- Confetti cake it.
- I'm gonna be a confetti cake.
- [laughs]
All right, first limo
pulling up the drive.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Hey, Hannah--
- I'm gonna be okay.
[laughs]
- Let the journey begin.
- Oh, shoot.
- Hannah!
- Whoo!
[all cheering]
- Look at her!
- Wow, she's beautiful.
- I see you, girl.
Ah, let's go!
- That's Miss Alabama
right there, folks.
♪
- [under breath]
It's okay. It's okay.
- Thank you.
[soft music]
- Hi.
- How you doing, Hannah?
- I'm good.
- You look awesome.
- Oh, thank you.
- I'm sorry.
I'm really nervous right now.
- Don't be nervous.
- Well, thank you for that.
My name's Garrett.
- Hey, Garrett.
- I'm actually from Birmingham.
- Oh, my gosh, yay!
- Yeah, we--
Yeah, we gotta represent
while we're here, right?
- That's right.
That's right.
- And I'm a golf pro.
- Okay, cool.
- And I know
you're gonna meet a lot
of people tonight.
- Yes.
- Maybe a few bogeys.
But I wanna be
your hole in one.
All right?
- That's awesome.
- Well, you look great.
- Thank you.
- I look forward to seeing you
inside, all right?
- It's nice to meet you.
- It's great to meet you, too.
- I like hearing that--
that twang.
♪
Aww, I liked him.
Hey.
- Hello, there.
- How are you?
- I'm amazing.
- I like that.
- You smell good.
- Oh, thank you.
- So, I wanted to give you
kind of an insight to who I am.
- Okay.
- So I kind of have, like,
the five Cs...
- Okay.
- That I live by.
Character, charm, charisma...
- Uh-huh.
- Consistency...
- Okay.
- And compassion.
You got them all?
- I got them all!
- And can I be very,
very honest?
- Yeah.
- You're very, very pretty.
- Oh, th--
- You're super pretty.
- I'm so glad that
you think I'm pretty.
That would be bad
if you didn't, so...
[both laughing]
What's your name?
- Mike Johnson.
I like it.
Strong name.
- Yes.
I look forward to seeing
you soon.
- Absolutely.
I'll see you inside.
♪
- How are you?
- Good, how about you?
- You look amazing.
- Oh, thank you.
You look great.
- I like your jacket.
It feels good.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
- My name's Jed.
- Hi, Jed.
- I'm from Nashville.
- Oh, southern boy.
I like it, yeah.
- I'm so excited to be here.
- Well, good.
- My family has always told me
how important it is
to shine inside and outside.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you're gleaming tonight.
You look amazing.
- I know.
I'm already, like, shining.
- You're already ahead
of the game.
- Like, this dress, but--
- You are.
- Hopefully the inside
will shine, too.
- I can't wait to get
to know your heart.
- Oh, nice to meet you, Jed.
- Nice to meet you.
See you in a bit.
- That's so sweet.
Yeah.
♪
- Wow.
- Hi.
- You are absolutely
killing that dress.
- Oh, thank you.
- You look amazing.
I'm Tyler.
- Hi, Tyler.
- I, uh, was so stoked
to find out that you were
the Bachelorette.
- Aww.
- So I had to fly all
the way here from Florida
to come and see you.
- Oh, wow.
- And, uh, I gotta say that
that smile's worth every mile.
- [laughs]
- Can't wait to see you inside.
I got something
in store for you.
- We're gonna have a fun time.
You look great.
- I'll see you.
- Yeah.
- Hi, Hannah.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- You look stunning.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- So, I can genuinely say that
I really wanted it to be you.
I think you're authentic
and that's--
- Thank you.
- That's really hard to find.
- Oh, thank you.
Well, I'm gonna be that
every step of the way.
So I hope you can be, too.
- Oh, I will be.
100%.
- Good.
Now, what was your name?
- Dylan.
- Dylan, okay.
Well, Dylan,
it's so nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes.
So I'll see you more inside.
- Definitely.
Can't wait to find you.
- Awesome.
- I'm not really sure
what Colton was thinking
letting Hannah go,
but thank God he did.
'Cause, I mean, she looks
unbelievably beautiful.
There's a lot of guys
coming tonight.
You only get one chance
at a first impression.
So I'm hoping that my action
stacks up well against them.
- Hannah!
♪
Hannah!
- Oh, hey.
♪
[laughs]
Yes!
Somebody's already
jumping fences for me.
Yeah.
- How's it going?
- Hey.
- It's so good to see you.
- Oh, thank--yes!
- Yeah, so you look amazing.
And I wanted to tell you that
every woman deserves a man
that will jump
a fence for them.
- Absolutely.
- And clearly I'm that guy
for you.
- Yeah, I love it.
- Yeah. Awesome.
- That was awesome.
- Cool.
Well, good to see you.
- It's so good to see you.
- Looking forward
to talking inside.
- I'll see you inside.
- Yeah, sounds good.
♪
[all cheering]
- Hey.
What's going on?
It's so great
to finally meet you.
- Oh, it's so good
to meet you, too.
- So, I do have
to be honest with you.
- Okay.
- 'Cause I know you're all
about honesty and transparency.
- I am, absolutely.
- I am a virgin.
- Okay.
- I'm just--I'm
just messing with you.
- I was like, "All right."
That's okay.
- I'm not, but I am a virgin
to this experience
and I'm so, like, excited
to go on this, you know,
journey with you, really.
- Yeah.
Well, I am so excited, too.
Virgin or not, hey.
What was your name again?
- Devin.
Devin, Devin.
Well, let's have
some fun tonight.
- I can't wait.
I can't wait.
- Yeah.
See you inside.
[quirky music]
He is cute.
Had some energy.
I liked it.
Hi.
- Hello.
So nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hi.
So, uh, my name
is John Paul Jones.
- Okay.
- My friends call me
John Paul Jones.
- Okay.
- So you can call me
John Paul Jones.
- John Paul Jones.
That's it.
- Yeah.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
John Paul Jones.
- So, I'll see you inside.
Yeah.
♪
- Say John Paul Jones
three times fast.
John Paul Jones.
Got it.
- Hi.
[laughing]
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- Oh, I'm great.
Hi, I'm Brian.
- Hi, Brian.
It's nice to meet you.
- It's fantastic
to finally meet you.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Suddenly, like, my--my heart
went into my throat
and my--it started
beating a million miles an hour
and I didn't know what to do.
You're crushing it already.
[both laughing]
There are no words,
and you're just going--
[chuckles]
Hi.
I'm--I'm Brian.
When I heard that you were
gonna be the Bachelorette...
- Yeah?
- I was so excited.
You just have this
awesome personality.
- Oh!
- Oh, I just want you to know
that I'm here to look
for a life partner and I am
really excited to l--
uh, see you inside.
- Yeah, it's gonna be great.
- It's gonna be great.
- What's your name, again?
- I'm Scott.
- Scott.
Well, it's nice to meet you.
- Yes.
It's really nice meeting you.
- Yeah.
I'll see you later, okay?
- I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
I'm so shocked by how nervous
every guy is
when they walk out
of the limo.
- You know that moment when
you--you have so many things
you want to say and then
somebody totally takes
your breath away?
- [laughs]
- Well, I'm experiencing it,
uh, for the first time
right now.
Um...
- Aww.
I just couldn't believe that
they were that nervous
to meet me.
Because I know myself
and I'm like,
"You really don't have anything
to worry about."
- I am so excited to be here
and have literally
the opportunity to come
and do this adventure with you.
- Yeah.
- Good.
- Bye.
- I'll see you in there.
- Oh, this way.
- Oh!
- You can tell the guys have
thought about what to say
for, like, multiple days.
- Since I found out that you
were gonna be the Bachelorette,
you've been in all
of my dreams.
- Really?
- So you are quite literally
the girl of my dreams.
- [laughs]
It's so cute.
And it made me feel
really good.
- I've been traveling
for the last, like,
four or five years and--
- Yeah.
- I was like,
"I won't have anything that
can top this moment."
And here we are.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, so...
- So nice to meet you.
- Can't wait to see you inside.
- Yeah.
I'm feeling excited
and hopeful
after just these small moments
of interaction.
- Look at you sparkling
all over the place.
- Hey.
- Hi, I'm Matt.
- Matt, it's nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
So I'm really excited
for what's to come tonight.
[beeping]
What is this?
Oh, it's a big package.
Hey!
[quirky music]
♪
[laughing]
[beeping]
I'm nervous.
- What's that?
- It's, like, a forklift.
[beeping]
- Oh, God.
♪
- It's a box.
- Oh, it's a box.
♪
- [laughs]
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
[beeping]
- It's, like, a forklift.
[gate creaking]
- It's a box.
- Oh, it's a box.
[beeping]
- I'm nervous.
[quirky music]
[laughing]
- Oh, something's gonna
come out of the box.
- No way.
♪
- [screams]
- [laughs]
Hannah, this package
isn't complete without you!
[both laughing]
- Okay.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- You look beautiful.
I'm Joe.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- He just showed his package.
- That's a bold move.
- I'm not sure if it's gonna
work out for him.
- I can't wait
to get to know you.
- Yes.
- And I just want you to know
that you check all of my boxes.
[both laughing]
- That was good.
What was your name, again?
- Joe.
- Joe, nice to meet you.
- Yeah, the box king.
- The box--the box king.
I like it.
- All right, see you inside.
- Well, I'll see you inside.
That was great.
- Yep.
Hannah was very surprised.
No one has ever popped
out of a box.
So it's gonna be hard to beat
because, you know,
I'm the box king.
Total package.
- [shushes]
["Rock-a-Bye Baby" plays]
- What you got?
- Guess we'll find out.
- [laughs]
- I wanted to give you
a glimpse of what
our future
can look like together.
- Okay.
- But first, let's start
this damn party!
- All right, let's do it!
- Seriously?
[all laughing]
- Ooh!
- Whoa!
Careful.
- The house is starting
to fill up.
There's a lot
of characters here.
- Hey.
- Bonjour, Hannah.
- Oh, bonjour.
- Uh, je m'appelle Connor.
[speaking French]
- Uh-huh.
[both laughing]
- And guys are coming into
the house at this point
at all angles.
- Roll tide, baby!
- Roll tide!
- Hi, Hannah.
- Hi.
- I'm Ryan.
- [laughs]
- Whoo!
- Hey, Ryan.
- It's so nice to--
- Oh, my gosh,
please don't fall.
- We got a lot of guys out
there trying anything
and everything to get
Hannah's attention.
- I thought maybe
you could give me a hand,
and together
we could tie the knot.
- Oh, that was good.
- She's meeting 30 of us guys,
so you just never know what
you're gonna expect
on night one.
- So it's a sausage
party tonight.
I have the mustard.
I hope we can relish
this evening...
and I'm gonna make sure we, uh,
"ketchup" inside.
- Oh.
- Does that sound good?
- Absolutely.
- Good?
- [laughs]
- Wonderful.
- I see a guy come in
eating a hot dog
with a pint of mustard.
- Gentlemen, how are you?
- I see another guy coming in
with roller skates on.
- Roll tide, baby.
[laughter]
- More guys continue
to pile in.
- With this pizza, will you
have a "pizza" my heart?
- Oh, absolutely.
- [laughs]
- Have a piece of your heart.
- Excellent.
- What am I here for?
Like, it's like
a football tryout?
- [groans]
- Well...
- Oh, fumble.
- Looks like I befumbled
that introduction.
- [laughs]
You used my word.
It was great.
- This thing is getting crazy,
man.
And it's just the first night.
[quirky music]
- Whoa!
- [snarls]
[exciting music]
[laughs]
Beast mode.
- That's right.
- Oh, my God!
Luke!
What's up?
- Gimme some for the beast.
Give me some love.
- That was awesome.
- So I know they call you
the beast.
- Oh, yeah.
- But I'm king of the jungle.
- Oh, okay.
- And I'm hoping that we can
change your title to my queen.
- Okay, we can see about that.
- All right.
- It was good to see you again.
- Well, give me a hug.
Let's go get this
party started.
- Yeah, absolutely.
You look great.
- Thank you.
You, too.
I met Hannah on
"After the Final Rose."
She instantly was like,
"Good to see you again, Luke."
Which I felt like was huge.
Boys, boys.
What's up?
She is just so cute
and giggly.
You know, just being herself
and you can tell she's genuine.
- I saw you on the "AFR"--
"After the Rose."
- Right.
- And you got your swole on
while you did a couple push-ups
before you put on your--
put on your suit.
- There was five of us that
got to meet her.
So I can tell the guys
in the house are jealous.
I mean, who wouldn't want
to be one of the first guys
to meet her?
- I know this isn't
the first time we met.
- No.
- But I just want to say,
like, you have such
a calming presence.
- Oh, good.
- It's a huge advantage.
And you just get another time
to have a first impression.
- Good to see you again.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad you remember me.
I can't wait to have a moment
with you inside.
- Absolutely.
Same.
- All right.
- How would you rate
the other guys?
- The Cam guy crushed it.
The one who came out
and rapped.
- How about Cam getting
a rose already?
- I mean, he definitely
deserved it.
- He's probably coming in
tonight, like,
he's super, like, no nerves.
I would love to know what he's
gonna do when he gets here.
- Yeah.
- Check, check.
This thing on?
- [laughs]
- All right, let's do this.
- Yes!
[laughs]
- ♪ I gotta keep it fresh
like I'm coming out the limo ♪
♪ What you know about me
this the rap demo ♪
♪ It's your boy Cam
and I'm back on the mic ♪
♪ I'm trying to live it up
like I'm living the hype ♪
♪ What you know about me
got a soul worth saving ♪
♪ I'm trying to win the game
like my name is Nick Saban ♪
♪ There's one thing I gotta say
I got more flow ♪
♪ This the final rose
and I'm ready to go ♪
- Oh, yes.
It's my favorite.
- Oh, it's so good
to see you again.
to see you, Cam!
- Yeah, I have been really
excited.
Uh, been thinking about you...
- Yes!
- And, um, you know,
I'm really looking forward
to this whole journey.
And I'll come find you
later tonight.
You got one more
surprise for you.
- Absolutely.
- All right.
Good to see you, girl.
- Rose looks good.
- Thank you.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
- There he is.
- Gentlemen.
Whoo!
- Oh, Mr. Rose showing it off.
- Hey, what's up?
- Your rap was pretty nice
the other day--I liked it.
- What was your name?
- Scott.
- Scott, Cam.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Cam.
- Good to see you again.
Good to see you again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's definitely a great
feeling knowing that
I'm pretty much guaranteed
more time with her.
- What'd you do today?
- I did another freestyle.
You know, I was spitting some
bars like Willy Wonka
so no big deal.
[laughter]
But I've gotta keep
the momentum going
because there's other
gentlemen in there that
are trying to go for the same
woman that I'm going for.
- How did you get so good
at freestyle rapping?
- Just A-B-C--
Always Be Cam.
I'm not here for my
15 minutes of fame.
I'm here for my lifetime
of love.
And I'm gonna show her that
I'm here for the long haul.
[motor revving]
- It's a tractor!
[country music]
- Whoo!
- Hey!
Whoo!
- No way.
Are you serious right now?
- Come on already!
♪
- Whoo!
- [grunts]
So I have a song for you.
- Oh, yes.
- Thank you, yes.
- Yes, yes.
- ♪ I'm Matt Donald
and I'm really nervous ♪
♪ And I hope I catch your eye
♪ There's a bro bro here
and a bro bro there ♪
- Hey.
- ♪ Here's a bro
♪ There's a bro
everyone's a bro bro ♪
♪ I'm Matt Donald
and I love your smile ♪
♪ And I hope I get a rose
- Aww, that was so good!
- Thank you.
So my name is Matt Donald.
- Okay.
- Growing up, my friends used
to call me Old Matt Donald.
- Okay.
- Hence the tractor...
- And that really bad song.
- It was great.
I liked it.
- Good.
Well, thank you.
I hope I made a good
impression with Hannah.
I want her to remember me
as the tractor guy.
Like, I mean, how else am I
gonna differentiate myself
from everybody else, you know?
- She's gonna remember
the hat for sure.
- Well, I was hoping she would
remember my name 'cause I know
you guys are all studly
gentlemen, I'm sure.
There's gonna be a lot of,
uh, guys that she's
meeting tonight so...
All the guys are such studs.
Gosh, this is gonna be
fierce competition for sure.
- Hi.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I'm Chasen.
- Chasen?
- Yeah, Chasen.
- Oh, I like that.
- So I was, like, goofing
around today in the hotel.
- Uh-huh.
- And I made you
a paper airplane.
- Paper airplane!
- Yeah.
So, gives you a little insight
to what I do.
Take off is my favorite part
of my job.
- Okay.
- And our relationship's
about to take off.
So I am really excited to start
this journey with you.
- Aww, I love that.
- I'm a commercial
airline pilot,
and women like a man
in uniform.
You know, I try to work that
to my benefit.
- [singsong] Nailed it!
- I have a lot to offer and I
think I can go the distance.
So I feel good about
this whole situation.
[uplifting music]
- Okay. Hi.
- Wow.
Hello there.
- [laughs]
♪
- You look so beautiful.
- Aww, thank you.
- Wow.
I'm Peter.
- Hi, Peter.
- It is so nice to meet you.
- You look nice.
A man in uniform.
That's good.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
- I'm glad.
So I got you a little
gift tonight.
- Okay.
- Uh, as a pilot, uh,
wings are something that's
very symbolic of our love
for aviation.
And when you earn them,
they always give you
a set of two.
- Okay.
- So, that being said...
- Aww!
- I would like to give you
this pair right here.
- Oh, my gosh.
Thank you!
- And, uh, I'm just hopeful
that at the end of this journey
you and I can fly
away together, so...
- Oh, that was so sweet.
I love this.
Thank you so much.
- I'm glad you enjoy it.
- It was nice to meet you,
Peter.
- You, too.
See you inside, okay?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- All right.
[soft music]
- He was really cute.
And a guy in a uniform
is always hot, so...
[overlapping chatter]
- Whoo.
What's up, guys?
[all speaking at once]
- Oh, man, we got another
pilot now.
- It's competition.
- Oh, man.
- Hey, I saw you on TV.
- Oh, there you go.
- How you doing? Jason.
- What's up, man?
- Nice to meet you.
- Peter, what's up?
I'm Joe.
- Hi, Joe.
It's nice to meet you.
- I lost words.
[laughs]
I almost came in
in my uniform tonight.
- You're a pilot, too?
- I am.
- No way.
- Yeah.
- So there's another pilot
here tonight.
Definitely shocked to see that
but all I can do is be me.
And hopefully, you know,
that's enough to warrant
a rose for tonight and just
kick this journey off
in the right way.
- All right, Hannah.
- Hey.
- You just met
your 30 bachelors.
- Yeah.
- It seems like you're
having a blast.
It seems like you are just
at ease and this is a regular
night for you.
- Yeah, it feels like that.
But I think it's because
the guys have been
so great, too.
- Well, before you go in...
- Mm-hmm.
- I want to remind you even
though you've already given out
one rose--Cam has his rose...
- Yes.
- There will be a
First Impression Rose.
- Okay.
- You're gonna give that rose
to the one guy that stands out
to you tonight
and you definitely want
to keep him around.
- Okay.
- I'll bring that in
a little bit later.
Do you think you know?
Is there somebody that already
kind of piqued your interest?
- There's a few that I'm
definitely interested
to get to know more,
but I don't have just somebody
in mind just yet.
- Yeah.
All right, are you ready
to go inside?
- Yes.
- Hannah, get ready
for the night of your life.
- Lord, in your goodness
and your love...
Let me be patient.
Give me...
Give me the words.
Help me feel worthy.
Help me feel smart.
- She's beautiful.
- Yeah.
I'm just looking forward
to seeing her again.
- Me, too.
[all laughing]
- Oh, my God.
- Here we go.
- Welcome.
[all cheering]
- [laughing]
Hey, y'all.
How--how is everybody?
- Amazing now.
- Good.
I'm so glad that
you're all here.
Um, I want to say first off,
thank you.
I'm just really thankful that
you all decided to say yes
to taking this chance with me.
Uh, I'm not perfect.
I'm going to stumble
over my words.
I'm gonna make mistakes.
And you are, too.
I don't want perfect.
I want real.
I'm gonna be real with you,
and I want you to be real
back in return with me.
And if you're not,
if that's not what you want,
then I'm not the girl for you.
Um, since I've been announced
the Bachelorette,
it's been hard to feel
like I deserve all this
and all of you guys.
And it wasn't until tonight
each of you--
the few moments that we had
together really made me feel
like I deserve this,
and I deserve to find love.
And because of that,
I can say that I can see
my husband in this room.
[upbeat music]
It's so crazy.
Um...
[all laughing]
But with that being said,
raise your glass...
[all laughing]
To a start of a wonderful night
and the beginning of an amazing
imperfect adventure
to find true love.
Cheers.
all: Cheers.
- Nailed it!
[all laughing]
- Well done.
Can I take you?
- Yes, come on.
- All right, follow me.
- Do you know where
we're going?
- Excuse me, fellas.
- And so we begin.
[laughs]
- Luke grabbed her
and walked out and I was like,
"Oh, he's going.
All right."
- All right, so I gotta
be honest with you.
- Okay.
- All right, you're the most
beautiful girl I've ever seen
in my life.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Dude swooped in.
He got in there.
- Survival of the fittest.
You just gotta get in there.
- Yeah.
- So tell me about yourself.
- I'm from Florida.
- Okay.
What part?
- Uh, Jacksonville.
- Okay.
- And I actually just recently
became an uncle.
- Oh, awesome.
- Yeah, it's been--
it's been amazing just to see
my brother and my sister-in-law
have their first child
and I know, like,
I feel like I'm behind,
you know?
I don't even have
a girlfriend, you know,
much less a fiancée or wife.
But I'm ready to get there.
- Same.
- And I'm not gonna lie.
This is the last place
I would picture myself.
- Same.
- Like, my--my sister-in-law
signed me up.
- Mm-hmm.
- And honestly I was like,
"There's no way I find
a girl that I could fall
in love with."
- Yeah.
- And then I saw--seriously--
episode one of Colton's season,
and I saw you.
Like,
"Hey, it's Alabama Hannah,"
and I was just like,
"That--that could be my wife."
I said that.
I'm not kidding.
- Oh, my gosh!
- And then here we are.
And I don't know you
all that well.
But I'm seriously really,
really into you.
So you got some
catching up to do.
You got some catching up to do.
- Well, you're doing all right.
- Yeah, I like that.
That makes me feel good.
[laughs]
I'm on a high right now
just from spending time
with Hannah.
I never thought I'd catch such
strong feelings so quickly.
- It's good to--
- Give the sweet lady
a nice hug.
Ah, I'm just--
I'm blown away.
- How are you feeling
throughout this process?
- I'm feeling excited.
- Definitely.
- Yeah.
- You're strong.
Oh, you are super strong.
- Thank you.
- When you came in there
and gave that speech to us--
I like a strong woman,
and you were--
you did that from--to a T.
- Yeah.
Well, thank you.
- Definitely so.
So you know what you want,
and that's good.
- I think it's just because
I know what I deserve.
But it's been a struggle
and I still struggle with it.
- Tell me about that.
I'm curious.
- So, um, I think
for so long in my life
I strived to be perfect.
And I started to finally
realize that the only way
I'm gonna be with somebody is
if I can be whole as a person.
- Love yourself first.
- Yeah.
- When you love yourself,
there is nothing
to hold you back.
- That's right.
Nothing at all.
- Yeah.
And that's why I'm still--
even though I still get
a little nervous but, like,
calm and excited about all this
because I do feel ready...
- Mm-hmm.
- For what's next.
- I think you're 100%
ready for what's next.
- Thank you.
- This is great.
- I am.
- Can you imagine, like,
waking up every morning
next to Hannah?
Like, taking her to dinner
and, like--
I mean it'd be incredible.
- Yeah.
- But knowing that you're
fighting for one girl
amongst awesome guys,
I mean, you really have
to step out and show
who you are.
- I'm looking around
and I'm seeing a lot
of eligible bachelors here,
and it is a little
bit intimidating
but I'm confident in who I am
and what I have to offer.
- You're the Bachelorette,
right?
- Yes.
- Well, I don't know that
anyone's thrown you
a proper bachelorette party.
So I figured, uh...
- Yes!
- I should be the one
to throw you
your first bachelorette party.
- Oh, my gosh.
Let's do it.
This is awesome.
- Okay, all right.
Let's check this out.
So, I got a bunch
of games set up here.
- Okay.
- I think the first game
we should play,
it's called Junk in the Trunk.
- Ready?
- Okay.
- And go!
[upbeat music]
Are they coming out?
- I don't know.
♪
- Yeah, there you go!
There you go!
Put your back into it!
That's good.
- [laughing]
- That's good.
[heavy breathing]
All right,
one more left.
Hold on, you got it.
- Don't touch my junk.
[laughs]
Not yet.
- You're the champion,
so I think it's only fitting
that we put the bachelorette
crown on you.
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
Okay.
- Oh!
[both laughing]
- Oh.
- Oh, my gosh!
- It's a perfect fit.
So beautiful.
All right, I am clearly
out of shape.
- Man.
Tighten up.
I'm just kidding.
- You're right.
- Being the Bachelorette
feels like a dream.
I guess I have been waiting
so long for this moment.
I mean, I was already excited
about tonight
but it's so much more
than I imagined.
- I'm not looking
for the perfect Hannah.
- Mm-hmm.
- I want the fun, quirky,
flirty, flaws and all, so--
- Awesome, well,
that's what you'll get.
Because I don't know
another way anymore.
- I'm ready for it.
Okay, good.
- Being with these guys
just feels natural.
There's no pressure
to be perfect.
They're just making me feel
really special.
- When you were
officially announced...
- Uh-huh.
- I was saying the whole time
that I hope it was you.
And I'm not just saying that.
I mean it.
- Thank you.
That's so sweet.
I definitely believe that
I can fall in love here.
Be in love here.
Have all the things
happen here.
"After the Final Rose"
was just really fun
because I felt like you just--
you brought it, man.
- Yeah.
- That was so cool.
- Yeah, well, I mean,
you're Hannah Beast.
And like I said,
I want to fall for you
like I fell for Hannah Beast
because that was
my favorite part because
you were just so much energy
and you were so much fun and--
and that's what I want
in a life partner.
- I think so, too.
- I'm the type of guy that,
when I have chemistry
with somebody,
I don't kiss them
on the first date,
especially if I'm really
into them.
- Mm-hmm.
- But seeing as that this
is our technically second date,
may I kiss you, Hannah?
- Yes, you can.
[mellow music]
♪
- I had an amazing
one-on-one with Hannah.
You know, I felt the physical
chemistry and I think that
she felt that same spark, too.
So I think I made
a good impression.
I got two collars.
There's room for another rose.
- Mr. Harrison.
- How's it going?
- How are you, sir?
- Uh-oh.
- Guys, how's it going?
- What's up, Chris?
- I'll leave this for Hannah.
See you guys in a bit.
[suspenseful music]
- Oh, man.
Well, there goes the mood.
- When Chris brought out
the First Impression Rose,
like, everything just
kinda stood still.
♪
- This is a big thing.
I mean, whoever gets this rose,
like, that's saying something
for the rest of this journey.
- I mean, I--I just think she's
looking for somebody who's
real, transparent, you know,
coming in here
with the right intentions.
Simple as that.
- Hannah made it very clear
from the beginning that
she wants all of us to be our
open and true self,
and if you're trying
to hide something,
the truth's gonna come out.
♪
- You ready to do this?
- Let's do it.
[mellow guitar music playing]
- ♪ Roll on over
with me, honey ♪
♪
♪ Underneath the starry sky
♪ Oh, roll tide
- [laughs]
- ♪ Oh, roll tide
- Yeah!
Damn.
That's really sexy.
Whew!
I have a total crush on Jed.
- ♪ Here by my side
♪ Mm, mm, mm
♪
- Oh, my gosh.
All these guys are so great.
I'm so lucky.
[sneaky music]
- This van is awesome.
- It's like
we're FBI Surveillance,
and I'm here for it.
- I feel very official.
- How are you?
- I am great.
How are you feeling?
- Good.
- I met a ton of guys.
- Hannah's taking this
very seriously,
and that is why
she invited me and Katie here
to scope out the guys tonight.
- Yeah, I was really nervous
coming out.
You are way more beautiful than
I thought you were gonna be.
- Oh, my gosh.
You're so sweet.
- I was--I really mean it.
- He's so sweet.
- I am so excited
to be here tonight.
I know there's some
really good guys here,
but unfortunately, there is
one guy I'm on the lookout for.
- I want you to know
you're not the only person
from Alabama.
- Okay.
- So, I was actually
born in Montgomery.
- Okay, yes, roll tide.
I love it.
- Roll tide, baby.
- Okay, this is not the guy.
Earlier today, someone reached
out to me on social media
saying that one of the guys
here has a girlfriend.
I don't know if this is true,
so I want to do, like,
some further investigating
to get to the bottom of it.
- Nice to see you, Matt.
- I wanna see if he has
the nerve to show up tonight.
I feel like we're Hannah's
guardian angels right now.
Hannah's Angels.
- Hannah's Angels.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you so much.
- Was that the biggest package
you've ever seen, or what?
- That was--it was--
it was nice.
- Oh, my God.
No.
- Well, I sell packaging
for a living,
and that's why
I jumped out of a box.
- Okay.
- So, I sell boxes.
- Okay, cool.
- Yeah.
I design.
I can make any type of box.
- Okay.
- Yeah, anything, any size.
- Okay, you better
make some boxes, okay?
- Yeah, to ship people away in.
- Yeah...
[laughter]
- Probably a bunch
of these people.
- Yeah...
[laughter]
[quirky music]
- Not my type for sure...
- So good to talk to you.
- But he's not the guy
with the girlfriend.
- How are you?
- I'm so good.
How are you?
- I'm good.
I got my wings.
- This is a--
This is a crazy night, huh?
- It is, but it's a good night.
- It is.
- Oh, he's cute.
- I'm just so happy to be here.
- I'm glad that
you're here too.
- So, I had a question now.
You, um--are your bags packed,
'cause I got the jet
waiting outside, so...
- [laughs] Yeah, let's go.
Where are we going?
- Okay. You tell me.
- Somewhere warm.
- I'm your pilot,
so somewhere warm?
I could do that.
I could bat with that.
- I've always wanted to learn
how to fly a plane.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- Well, this is, like,
the perfect guy to teach you.
- That would be really fun.
So that's, like, your childhood
dream, to be a pilot?
Or did it just,
like, one day, you--
- It was, yeah.
So, it's kinda crazy.
My whole family's, like,
an aviation family, so...
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, my dad--he's a pilot.
My mom's a flight attendant.
- That's so cool.
So, you all
share that together.
- So, it's a pretty cool bond.
- Yeah.
- I'm getting, like--
she's liking him.
- I'll see you later,
all right?
- Yes, for sure.
- All right, bye.
- That guy was a good one.
- Yeah, he's definitely not
the guy with the girlfriend.
- How are you, Scott?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- Good.
- How's your evening been
so far?
- It's going good.
How about yours?
- It's--it's better now.
I was so nervous
walking out of that limo...
- Yeah?
- And just seeing you.
Kinda took my breath away
a little bit.
- Aww, you're so sweet.
- I'm not gonna lie.
- Oh, my God.
That's him.
That's the guy
with the girlfriend.
- So, I--I'm here
to find a life partner.
I'm here to be--
find the one for me.
- Yeah.
- And I think you are too.
- Same, yeah.
I think that's great.
- And so,
I love interior design.
I think
it'd be awesome to, like,
kinda map out our dream home.
- Yeah, I did interior design.
- Really?
Oh, I didn't know that.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
I'm just trying to get
a feel of, like, you know,
what you like.
- Okay.
- Let's go with
the kitchen first.
- I like modern kitchens
with rustic undertones.
- Totally agree.
I'm someone who has
very expensive tastes.
I like luxury stuff.
- Same.
- I'm from Chicago, so
I live in the city right now.
I live in, like,
a high-rise building.
- Okay.
- Have you ever been
to Chicago?
- I haven't, no.
- What?
You haven't been?
You gotta come visit me.
- I'm gonna have to.
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
What a douche.
- It was a pleasure
getting to talk to you.
- We have to warn her.
[dramatic music]
- What's up, fellas?
I was looking for Hannah.
- She's in the house
somewhere.
- Okay.
- He's on a mission.
I guess it must've been
something pretty serious.
- I'm so excited
to be out here and
doing this.
- Yes, definitely.
- Yeah, it was so nice
to talk to you tonight.
- You as well, all right?
- [laughs]
- Um, need to talk to you.
- Okay.
- You got a sec? All right.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Come with me.
How you doing?
- I'm doing good, I think.
I feel like I'm doing good.
Am I doing good?
[laughs softly]
- That was kinda weird.
What was that about?
- I'm not sure.
- That makes me--
that makes me nervous.
- Hey, girls.
both: Hey.
- Hey!
- Hey, my girl.
- Oh, my God.
How has it been going?
- How do you feel?
- I feel great.
- Hi, baby.
- I--What's--Okay,
What's been happening?
- How did you feel about Scott?
- Um, I liked Scott.
He was nice.
- So, Scott apparently
has a girlfriend.
[dramatic chords]
- Have all you guys
talked to Hannah already?
- Yeah.
I think we just hit it off.
I actually, like, planned out
like a dream home with her.
We kinda picked out some
different pictures and stuff.
- She's an interior designer,
right, so...
- I know, like, I knew that
she was into that kinda thing.
- I've read messages
between the girlfriend and her
friends of her talking about
how they saw each other Monday
before he came.
He told her
they're gonna be together
whenever this is all over,
and they're gonna
go on a trip together.
- I thought my time
with Hannah was awesome.
My intentions is to be
with her long-term.
I mean, I guess it hasn't
totally set in that
she could be my wife.
However,
I totally think that
she could be.
[door rattles]
- So, do we have any intel
on Hannah?
- She's been gone
for a while now.
- Uh-oh.
There she is.
- There's our girl.
- Whoo.
- Come on in.
- Hey, Scott.
We need to talk.
- Okay.
- Yeah, come on.
- Oof.
- Ooh.
Oh, damn.
- That didn't sound like
the most positive, like...
- There's something going on.
Ooh.
- Hannah walks in and she says,
"Scott, come with me."
And I'm just like, oh, man.
This isn't good for Scott.
- Was that a good "Let's talk"?
- No, probably not.
- No?
- I would not wanna
be him right now.
Ooh, man.
Ah.
- I can't wait to see this.
- Get him, girl.
[insects chirping]
- Was that a good "Let's talk"?
- No, probably not.
- No?
- She looked pissed off.
- Yeah.
- She didn't even acknowledge
any of us.
She just said,
"Scott, we need to talk."
- She did not look like,
"Hey, I'm coming to give you
a First Impression Rose."
- So,
I knew you were nervous
coming in today.
- Mm-hmm.
- It might be because
you have a girlfriend.
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- Okay.
Well, I've heard that
you do have a girlfriend.
- Okay.
- That you talked to her
on Monday,
so I just, like,
want to understand
why these things
would be said about you,
and exactly why you're here.
- Yeah, no, I mean,
I think that the reason
why you've heard that is,
I have, like, dated this girl,
and...
[clears throat]
I was nervous
coming into it, yeah,
like everybody else was,
but I'm not here for--
like, the reason
I'm here is for you.
I came here to get a long-term
relationship with someone
who I can be partnered with
going forward.
And, like, the fact that
I had dated a girl before--
- Like, on Monday?
No.
- Did you talk to her
on Monday?
- She--yeah,
she messaged me on Monday,
but that doesn't mean, like...
[tense music]
- Okay.
The first thing you said to me
was that you were so serious
about this, and I'm...
- I am serious.
That's why I'm here.
I wouldn't, like, come here
to fake all this stuff.
Everything that
I'm saying to you
has been honest and real
up to this point.
If I felt like there was an--
- Up to this point?
- Yeah, well, I just met you.
- This is--
- So, like, I have no idea
how it was gonna go.
I had no idea--
- So, you just
kept your girlfriend
back at home just to be safe.
♪
- [sighs softly]
I could understand how
it would come off that way.
- Mm-hmm.
- But that's not why.
- But your girlfriend
still thinks that--
- But we're not--she's not...
- So you're not together
'cause you're here,
but your girlfriend thinks that
you're coming back for her
after all this is done.
- I don't--
- And, like, that's not okay.
There's 29 other guys
in there
that I'm hoping are here
for the right reasons
and don't have other girls
just waiting at home
if this doesn't work out,
and you're here
and taking up so much time.
It's not fair to me.
It's definitely not fair
to that girl who thinks that
she's your girlfriend
back at home.
If you're not here
for what I'm wanting,
then it's your chance
to leave, and--
- I mean,
do you want me to leave?
- I want answers right now.
- Well, I'm telling you.
Yes, I was dating a girl
before I got on the show--
up until Monday, if you want
me to be completely honest.
Yes, up until Monday.
- [scoffs]
- If that bothers you,
I'm sorry, but do I think that
this is someone who
I'm going to marry long term?
No.
I don't.
You know, I've dated
other girls in the past.
- Do you know what
the end of this is?
It's an engagement.
- I understand that.
- So, on Monday...
- Yeah.
- You were just
in a relationship
with somebody else.
- But we were never, like,
serious boyfriend
and girlfriend, like--
- Okay, what you think of
as, like,
being serious about somebody
is very different
than what I think being
serious about somebody is.
Tha--no, let me talk.
- I am.
- No, let me talk.
You were about to.
- [strained chuckle]
- How dare you, like, come here
and think this is okay.
How is that
being serious about this?
- If you want to get
this upset with me,
it's totally fine, but
I could also say that
you just dated Colton
for the last, like,
two months, three months.
Like, you were just
madly in love with him,
and then all of a sudden,
now this is like
the same exact thing--
- [scoffing]
Okay.
It's not the same exact thing.
- It's pretty similar.
I wouldn't say
it's the same thing,
but it's similar.
- Oh, my gosh.
You are such a jerk,
and it's not the same at all.
- I...[laughs]
- You have another girl at home
that you still have on the line
and that is [bleep].
And so, you know what?
I'm...
I'm done with this.
There's no reason for you to
be here if you're not serious.
It's time for you to head out.
- Well, I'm telling you.
I have been here, and I--
- No, you haven't, dude.
Like, if that's what
you think is serious,
then, like, you have
a lot to get ready for
before you're ready for
any type of engagement.
- Oh, she's pissed.
- She's not messing around.
- I can hear her right now.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- So, let's--
- I'm sorry you feel that way.
- Uh, yeah, I do.
So, let's go.
- Okay.
- What's happening?
- They're coming in.
all: [shushing]
- Come on.
♪
No, come on.
- I'm coming.
♪
- Holy moly.
- That did not feel good.
- Ooh.
- Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
♪
- Good luck tonight.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
Good luck.
- Get to steppin', Scott!
Whoo!
[whispers]
He's right next to the van.
- Hey.
- Um, so,
Scott, um--
he had a girlfriend back home.
♪
The first thing I said
when I got here was
my greatest fear was somebody
was gonna be here
that wasn't gonna be real,
and wasn't here
for the right reasons--
for me.
And it's already happened.
So, if there's anybody else
that has something else
back home,
please leave now
because that's so disheartening
and so disrespectful to me
and to everybody else here
that's here for this
for real.
So, like...
anybody?
♪
I need a second because
that was totally ridiculous.
♪
Kay.
- Take a moment.
- Take your time.
♪
- Oh, [bleep].
- [sobs]
- That definitely kills
the mood for the night.
- Yeah, that did.
- Thanks, Scott.
- That guy sucks.
Seriously, like, don't come
here if you have a girlfriend.
- That crosses a big line.
- [sniffs]
- She's gonna be on her guard.
- Can you blame her?
Somebody lied
straight to her face.
We don't even know what to do.
Everyone's just standing there
kinda sitting on their hands.
We're all genuinely
worried that
the night's just
gonna end right there.
- [exhales]
[insects chirping]
- Oh, my God.
[exhales]
[soft dramatic music]
- It's hard to see her
be so upset from,
you know, when we got here,
seeing her so happy
and overwhelmed with joy
to meet all of us.
- She feels betrayed.
- Hannah told us that Scott
had a girlfriend back at home,
and she kicked him out.
Then she proceeded
to walk outside.
- [sighs]
- The worst part is,
we've already drained an hour
on this whole Scott thing,
so it's, like,
one more hour that we won't--
we don't get to talk to her.
- It sucks, but it could
be an opportunity
for the people
who haven't talked to her
to really step in
and restore her faith.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but sometimes
you just don't wanna
rush into something
like that, you know?
You just wanna give her
a little time to...[inhales]
take a deep breath
and just kinda
soothe and relax and then...
- I'm sure.
- Come back fresh start, yeah.
[somber piano music]
- [sniffs]
♪
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you feeling?
- [laughs] I'm so cold.
- I really wanna
make sure she's okay.
So, I thought I'd take that
initiative to just step up.
Come on, let's take a walk.
- Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
- Where did Luke go?
[both sigh]
- You good?
- Yeah.
Freezing.
- Well, I just want
to encourage you.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I know that
it's hard to see someone not
be here for the right reasons.
And it's just--
it hurts me to see you
just be so
caught off guard by that.
- Yeah.
I mean, I don't know you guys.
I don't know,
like, why you're here,
and the first thing
he said to me sitting down
was that he was
so serious about this.
And then to come
right out, like--
he had a girlfriend on Monday?
- What?
- Like, you know, like--
I don't know.
Like, I'm trying to just,
like, trust it'll be okay,
but I don't know
how people can do that, so...
- Well,
I just want you to know that
I am here for you.
I'm not here to earn
a couple roses.
Like, I'm here
to win your heart.
I'm here for you.
- I feel it.
[laughter]
- Well, that makes me happy.
[hopeful music]
- Oh.
Thank you.
The drama with Scott
totally, like,
[bleep] me up a little bit
in the head
and took up a lot of time
and a lot of my energy.
- I know that was like
a lot that happened earlier.
- Yeah, like...
- You feel all right?
- I mean, that I was kinda
fed some [bleep]
for a little bit, like,
was frustrating,
but ultimately,
I don't wanna focus on that.
I wanna focus on the people
that are actually here for me
and to give this a chance.
This is my life, my future,
and it's just disheartening
to know that
somebody came here
with the wrong intentions.
But I'm just trying
to stay focused
on the positives things
of tonight.
- I'm so sorry for
whatever went down before.
- Yeah.
- That's not okay.
- No, that's not okay.
- And I want you to know
I'm here for you,
and I'm super excited
about this journey.
- The guys have been so sweet
and so affirming to me.
And even though
I'm still a little nervous,
I am hopeful that
this can work.
- I wanted you to know that
I'm really excited
to be here for you.
Coming in here,
it was a little skeptical.
- Yeah.
- But when we met
after the final rose, you know,
when I actually
walked out and saw you,
I just felt so comfortable.
- Aww, good.
- And seeing you, like, I--
at least, I felt a connection.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, I'm not skeptical now.
- Yeah. [laughs]
- Just excited, you know?
- Yeah.
- But, uh, yeah.
- I'm glad that I've, like,
made you feel more comfortable.
- Yeah.
- And hope I always do.
And I think as long as
you continue to be, like,
open and yourself,
and super honest about
how you're feeling...
- Yeah.
- Then, like, we'll progress.
So, that's all
I'm gonna ask from you.
- Absolutely.
- And I'm just really glad
you're here.
- Yeah, same.
- [laughs]
♪
- That was good.
- Yeah.
Aww, it makes me
really excited.
- Good.
- Yeah.
I'm feeling on a little bit
of a high right now.
- [laughs]
- I don't even know if this
is gonna air or not, but...
- So cute.
- I'm really excited about us.
- I am too.
It's gonna be fun.
- We had a good conversation,
and sealed it with
a solid kiss, you know?
I feel very confident
about getting
a First Impression Rose.
It was good.
- Who's gonna get
the First Impression Rose?
- Anybody feel confident
that they did?
- Yeah, I do.
- You'll get two
First Impression Roses?
- Pre-impression,
First Impression.
- Speak of the devil.
- There she is.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Hey, Hannah.
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
♪
- I'm just curious
who she's gonna give that
First Impression Rose to.
- Yeah.
- I'll be ho--I feel good.
- You feeling pretty good?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
We'll--we'll see.
- [laughs]
What's up?
- Oh.
There she goes.
- Whew.
It's tough.
- Hey.
- Oh, there she is.
- Hello.
- Hi.
♪
- Luke?
- Yes?
- Will you come with me?
- [laughs] Yes.
- Hey.
- All right.
- Hey...[laughs]
- Good to see you again.
- It's good to see you.
- You doing well?
- I am.
- Awesome.
- [sighs]
- Um, so, I just wanna say...
You said to me that you,
like, already felt something
as soon as you saw me, and...
- Day one.
[laughter]
- And I feel
the exact same way.
- Mm.
- I'm excited when
I get to talk to you.
- [laughs]
Yes.
- And I look forward to
getting to know you better.
- Amen...
[laughter]
- So...
- Likewise, likewise.
- I really like you,
and I wanted you to know that.
So...
Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- Without a doubt.
- [laughs]
- Good. Okay.
- Seriously, though,
I just want you to know, like,
this seriously
means the world to me.
- Good.
- And the affirmation
that you've given me
has just been, like--
I feel like I'm living
an absolute dream right now.
[laughs]
This is amazing.
- You've, like, pulled all the
stops, and it's been so great.
I think that's right.
Oh, gosh.
There we go.
- Thank you.
- [murmurs, giggles]
- [laughs]
Thank you.
Seriously.
[rousing music]
♪
[both laugh softly]
Whew.
I am just ecstatic.
My heart is
literally exploding.
You're amazing.
- Thanks.
- Seriously.
- You're cool too.
[laughter]
- Before I met Hannah,
I knew that there was gonna
be something strong between us.
And after tonight,
I can totally already
see myself falling
madly in love with her,
and spending the rest
of my life with this girl.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Is it okay if I
get a seat right here?
- Sure.
- All right.
[men grunting]
- How is everybody?
men: Good.
- Good?
Good.
[glass clinking]
- Hey, hey.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
[overlapping greetings]
- What's up, Chris?
- I hate to break up the party,
but it is that time.
- Okay.
- Hannah, come join me.
- All right.
[soft dramatic music]
- Thank you all so much
for just being here tonight
and sharing your hearts
with me.
Unfortunately, we had
something happen tonight
that did take away
a lot of time, and so,
for those of you that I didn't
get a chance to talk to,
I am sorry about that.
But you all were so great.
And I have
really big decisions to make.
I've just gotta go with my gut,
what my heart tells me to do,
and I'll see you
at the rose ceremony.
- All right, fellas.
[dramatic music]
♪
[low conversations]
- It is what it is.
- Anybody feeling more nervous?
- Yeah, I'm pretty nervous
about it.
Scott took a lot of time
away from the rest of us,
so, I mean,
I didn't get time with Hannah.
And I feel pretty shaky
going into this rose ceremony.
- [sighs]
[bleep], dude.
That entire Scott situation
really screwed me over,
so it's not looking good.
- I'm very, very worried.
I didn't get any
one-on-one time,
and not having that time really
just is a bullet in the foot.
I feel like everyone that
didn't get to talk to her
could potentially
go home tonight.
[tense music]
♪
- Going into
the first rose ceremony
is one of the most
high-pressure situations
I've ever been in.
I am definitely
freaking out right now.
A lot of guys haven't gotten
a chance to talk to Hannah
because of the situation
with Scott.
And there are certainly
a number of guys
that are going home
because of it.
- Hey, guys.
[overlapping greetings]
It's been a long night,
and we did run out of time,
so I'm so sorry.
But I've been so appreciative
of every conversation
that I've had with you all.
To those that don't
receive a rose tonight,
I'm just having to go with
what my heart tells me to do
and I am really thankful
that you came
to meet me tonight.
♪
Mike.
- Oh, wow.
[both laugh]
Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
- Mike...[laughs]
Will you accept this rose?
- 100%.
- Awesome.
Okay, I think--is it this way?
- I think it's this way.
- Okay.
- We're learning this together.
- That's right.
Thank you.
- [muffled] Thank you.
♪
- Connor.
Connor S.
Connor,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Awesome.
[laughs softly]
Thank you.
- I'm here to
fall in love with Hannah
and have Hannah
fall in love with me.
- Matthew.
- Yes.
- But with Scott
pulling his crap,
that kinda cut our night
shorter.
- Matthew,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course I do.
Yes.
- So, I didn't
get time with Hannah,
and I'm kinda
sweating bullets over it.
- Connor J.
- Gentlemen.
Thank you.
[exhales]
Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Connor J.,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Thank you, Connor.
- Merci beaucoup.
[both laugh]
- And I'm hopeful that
she saw something
in our time together.
- Jed.
- Yes!
- And she wants to keep me
around a little bit longer.
- Jed,
will you accept this rose?
- I will.
- Awesome.
- But you could be on the
cutting block today and,
you know, that's it.
[dramatic music]
- Dustin.
♪
Dustin,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- Awesome.
Joey.
Joey,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Awesome.
- As these roses
are being given out,
I'm looking
intensely at Hannah.
- Devin.
- "You can--
you can call my name now.
You can call my name now.
You can call my name now."
- Peter.
- But each time I say that,
it's, like,
less and less confident.
- Dylan.
♪
- It's tough seeing people
walk in front of you.
- Dylan,
will you accept this rose?
- Always.
- So, that's difficult.
- Matteo.
Matteo,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- Did I say your name right?
- Yeah.
- Okay...
[laughs]
- [muffled]
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hannah is truly remarkable,
but I didn't get any
one-on-one time.
I didn't get a chance
to prove to her
who I was an individual.
- Jonathan.
- You're like, wow, I'm not
even good enough for one rose?
- Jonathan,
will you accept this rose?
- It'd be my honor.
- I'm losing my mind.
- Tyler C.
- So, I am kinda just
trying to come to terms
with the fact that
I'm going home.
- Tyler,
will you accept this rose?
- I'd love to.
Tyler G.
- I start to doubt myself.
- Tyler,
will you accept this rose?
- I'd be honored.
- I don't want her
to think that I'm here,
like, trying to have
a joke of a night.
Like, I really, really
do wanna get to know her.
- Daron.
- Whew.
- [laughs]
- I've been excited
ever since I found out
Hannah B. was
the Bachelorette.
- Daron,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- I--you know, I've lost sleep
'cause of excitement.
- Luke S.
Luke,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
♪
- Garrett.
Garrett,
will you accept this rose?
- I sure will.
- My palms are sweaty.
I could be going home
on the very first day
without ever getting a chance
to get to know her.
- Grant.
- I didn't come
all the way out here,
I didn't forego a promotion...
- Grant,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Certainly don't wanna
tell my friends or family
that I came out here
for a few days
to not get any time
to speak with Hannah.
- Kevin.
- [exhales]
- [laughs]
- If I don't
get a rose tonight,
I'd be totally crushed.
- Kevin,
will you accept this rose?
- I would love to.
- Thank you.
- Hannah, gentlemen.
It's the final rose tonight.
When you're ready...
♪
- John Paul Jones.
John Paul Jones,
will you accept this rose?
- With gratitude.
- Perfect.
- Thanks so much.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
If you have not
received a rose,
take a moment,
say your good-byes.
- It was great
talking to you, man.
[indistinct chatter]
- Ah.
It was nice meeting you, man.
- Bye, Ryan.
- At least your smile
warmed us up tonight.
- Thank you so much.
- [chuckles]
- It sucks.
I mean, it hurts.
I'm not gonna lie.
- Hannah, good luck.
Have a good one.
- Thank you.
I appreciate it.
- I was really excited.
Unfortunately, it just didn't
go the way I wanted it to.
Best of luck to you.
I hope you fall in love.
- Thank you.
- I think Hannah had a guy
who was willing to
put it all out there for her,
and unfortunately,
I don't think
Hannah saw that side.
I think she saw just,
like, a goofy--
you know, this guy's
just here to have fun,
which was actually
the exact opposite of who I am.
This was a little bit
of a heartbreak.
It's gonna take me some time
to kinda recover from this
and regain some confidence.
I mean, this sucks.
- Oh, man.
It was nice meeting you.
- It was nice meeting you too.
- I'm so sad.
Take it easy.
- Thank you.
- All right, good luck.
- Thank you for the package.
- No problem.
[laughter]
- Thank you, Hannah.
- So nice to meet you.
- It was very nice to meet you.
Sorry I couldn't get
any more time in, but...
- Well, thank you so much
for coming out.
- You're welcome.
Your husband's here.
Take care.
Obviously, there was a little
bit of drama this evening,
which took away
some time from everybody.
I don't wanna
blame it entirely
on that whole situation.
I am certainly bummed out
that I couldn't have...
done more.
I mean, she's such
a perfect girl inside and out.
She's perfect.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, yeah, please.
- I'm just--
I can't stress enough
how happy I am for her.
Really.
[sniffing]
- Cheers to this
beautiful adventure
we're about to go on.
Let's do it.
- To adventures.
all: Cheers.
- Whoo!
[all cheering]
- Stay tuned for
exciting highlights
from this season of
"The Bachelorette."
- And now it's a special
sneak peek
at this season of
"The Bachelorette."
- Ha ha!
Oh, my freak!
- My buns are out too here.
- [laughing]
[both screaming]
- [chanting]
Hannah! Hannah! Hannah! Hannah!
- How do y'all feel
in your kilts, huh?
- Hannah's about as real
as it gets.
She's not an actress.
She's not a movie star.
She's just a real girl
that's looking for love.
- Ooh.
- Ooh!
- I want a tough man,
someone I know
can grab a hold of me
and be like,
"That's my woman.
Roar, baby."
- Aah!
- Oh, my God.
I don't know what's happening.
- Why do you have a rubber?
What do you think's gonna
happen in this car?
- You put that in there.
God, that's so bad.
- What is wrong with me?
Holy ham.
I'm in Amsterdam!
[dramatic music]
I'm loving this!
- Oh, my goodness!
Look at that!
- Love is definitely
in the air,
and we're right there
on the same page.
- I truly can see a life
with you.
My heart right now is, like,
just filled with happiness.
- This is it, this is what
it's supposed to feel like.
- To be really honest, like,
I'm falling hard for you.
We could build our dreams
together...
- I wanna hear you say that.
- I do care.
I see myself
at the end of this
getting down on one knee.
- I felt that spark
and that connection.
I knew I was falling in love.
- Damn, you could cut that
sexual tension with a knife.
Ooh!
- [laughing]
- Do you wanna kiss me?
- Yes.
I'm completely and madly
in love with her,
and the chemistry
is undeniable.
- When it's real love,
there are no boundaries,
and I've fallen deeper
and deeper in love.
- Everything around me
was, like, spinning,
and I just saw your face.
It was in that moment
that I, like, looked at you
and I was like, "I'm falling
in love with you."
- This is so [bleep] up.
I would never do that
to anybody.
- If you're not here
for your wife,
get the [bleep] out of here.
- I can only be true to me.
I can only be Cam.
I always say A-B-C--
Always Be Cam.
- You can't reason
with a sick mind.
Like, you cannot reason
- Honestly, my trust
has, like...
been completely broken.
[all shouting]
- We all know that Luke P.
is an evil pathological liar.
- I'm so freaking nervous.
I don't know if I...
I can see it just yet.
- I don't care what
you said to her.
I've been nothing but truthful,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
- I'm here for Hannah,
and don't you ever [bleep]
forget it.
- You're violent.
You're aggressive.
You are a psychopath.
[man roaring]
- Whoa!
- That ain't no joke!
That ain't no joke!
- It's crazy.
He's literally insane.
- I'm obviously struggling.
This is my life,
and I can't control
when things are gonna hit me.
[thunder booming]
I cannot believe
you just said that to me.
I don't owe you anything
at this point.
Do you not understand that?
You don't own me.
You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do,
because first of all,
you're not my husband,
and even my husband,
the person I'm gonna be with,
is gonna allow me to be
my own person.
Get the [bleep] away from me.
I believe that sex was made
for a man and a woman
in marriage.
But I am having
physical relationships,
and honestly, like,
I have had sex.
And Jesus still loves me.
How dare I be judged by a man?
[whimpers]
I'm a normal human being,
like, trying to be
the Bachelorette,
and I don't know what to do.
And I'm scared.
[dramatic chords]
- "I'm gonna ship myself
in a box full of popcorn.
It's a great idea."
Son of a bitch.
[quirky music]
Nobody thinks about me.
[bleep] Joe.
♪
[grunts]
What the hell's wrong
with getting out of a limo
like everybody else?
This girl better find love.
[grunts]
[sighs]
♪
Literally.
No one else works here?
♪
[grunts]
You know what?
Pffft.
That's good enough.
[sighs]